[{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980253472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":21066,"timeElapsed":69336},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":14301,"timeElapsed":83642},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4617,"timeElapsed":88261},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980275635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3235,"timeElapsed":91500},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5585,"timeElapsed":97090},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":100207},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5161,"timeElapsed":105374},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":109740},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4471,"timeElapsed":114215},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6459,"timeElapsed":122620},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2313,"timeElapsed":124937},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2263,"timeElapsed":127205},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980313315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1972,"timeElapsed":129180},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980316139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2820,"timeElapsed":132004},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980318221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":134086},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":137239},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":141243},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3387,"timeElapsed":144634},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":12611,"timeElapsed":158407},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":161124},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":163356},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":165481},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3993,"timeElapsed":169479},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":172566},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980359871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":175736},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2737,"timeElapsed":178477},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2446,"timeElapsed":180927},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5706,"timeElapsed":187661},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2321,"timeElapsed":189986},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2194,"timeElapsed":192184},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2153,"timeElapsed":194341},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":197326},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":200132},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":202742},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2101,"timeElapsed":204847},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2395,"timeElapsed":207245},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7463,"timeElapsed":215518},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4956,"timeElapsed":220477},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2783,"timeElapsed":223263},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2107,"timeElapsed":225373},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":227474},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2361,"timeElapsed":229839},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2667,"timeElapsed":232510},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2225,"timeElapsed":234738},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":236681},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7953,"timeElapsed":245562},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1928,"timeElapsed":247495},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433837,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":249702},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1807,"timeElapsed":251513},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1646,"timeElapsed":253162},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":255861},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1621,"timeElapsed":257486},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":259909},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":262358},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2289,"timeElapsed":264651},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7780,"timeElapsed":273357},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1882,"timeElapsed":275243},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":277732},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1975,"timeElapsed":279711},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":281808},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":284512},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2922,"timeElapsed":287438},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3044,"timeElapsed":290487},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":292855},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":8650,"timeElapsed":302375},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1996,"timeElapsed":304376},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1621,"timeElapsed":306001},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1450,"timeElapsed":307454},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":309819},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2889,"timeElapsed":312710},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":315666},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":317881},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":320330},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":9277,"timeElapsed":330599},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2852,"timeElapsed":333454},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2406,"timeElapsed":335862},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529322,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9321,"timeElapsed":345187},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3852,"timeElapsed":349044},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2537,"timeElapsed":351585},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":354884},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3239,"timeElapsed":358127},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3537,"timeElapsed":361667},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2597,"timeElapsed":364267},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4771,"timeElapsed":370191},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2069,"timeElapsed":372264},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":374266},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":376573},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2540,"timeElapsed":379116},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2053,"timeElapsed":381174},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":383848},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2449,"timeElapsed":386301},{"subjectID":"r6b5nyycb3","prolificID":"5f79bca83a2eb65c0983816d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f3455ec38efa571f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":388448}]